{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649208074","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649208073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649211725","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649211725"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649215285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649215285"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649218777","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649218776"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649222147","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649222147"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649225634","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649225634"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649229106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649229106"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649232599","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649232599"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649236141","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649236141"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649239669","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649239669"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649245058","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649245058"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649248190","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649248190"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649251760","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649251760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649255030","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649255030"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649258873","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649258873"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649263761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649263761"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-g"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649267152","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649267151"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649270482","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649270482"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649273623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649273623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_l-i-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649277664","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649277663"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_f-r-t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649280960","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649280960"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649284060","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649284059"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-u-y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649287339","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649287339"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649290549","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649290549"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-v-u"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649294393","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649294393"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649300178","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649300177"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649306745","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649306744"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" 54f9e7f0-7ebe-46fa-9e7b-f23a622ea7b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649317700","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649317699"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mlango"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649321353","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649321353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mlango"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649322919","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649322919"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkono"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONO"," userResponse":" MKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649326479","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649326479"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkono"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649328047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649328047"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mvua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUA"," userResponse":" MVUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649331199","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649331199"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mvua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649332761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649332761"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maharage"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649336557","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649336557"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maharage"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649338112","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649338112"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mamba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649341883","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649341883"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mamba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649343442","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649343442"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAFUNZI"," userResponse":" MWANAFUNZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649348047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649348047"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAFUNZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649349614","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649349614"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mashua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUA"," userResponse":" MASHUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649352824","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649352824"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mashua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649354381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649354381"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpapai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPAPAI"," userResponse":" MPAPAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649358055","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649358054"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpapai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPAPAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649359611","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649359611"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649363314","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649363314"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649364873","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649364873"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649368392","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649368392"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649369951","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649369951"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwembe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEMBE"," userResponse":" MWEMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649373469","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649373469"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwembe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649375026","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649375025"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpira"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649377882","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649377882"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpira"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649379437","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649379436"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mchicha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHICHA"," userResponse":" MCHICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649382970","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649382969"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mchicha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHICHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649384528","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649384527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" meza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEZA"," userResponse":" MEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649387961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649387960"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" meza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649389527","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649389526"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649400935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649400934"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" START_MAZIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649421613","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649421613"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649423260","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649423259"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649426335","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649426334"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649427999","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649427998"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649431442","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649431442"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649433035","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649433034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mswaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSWAKI"," userResponse":" MSWAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649460910","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649460909"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mswaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MSWAKI"," userResponse":" START_MSWAKI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649479074","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649479074"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mswaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MSWAKI"," userResponse":" START_MSWAKI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649480700","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649480700"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mswaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSWAKI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649482335","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649482334"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" muhogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUHOGO"," userResponse":" MUHOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649488647","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649488647"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" muhogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUHOGO"," userResponse":" MUHOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649490240","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649490239"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" MBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649498508","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649498508"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" MBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649500139","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649500138"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBU"," userResponse":" MBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649507394","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649507393"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBU"," userResponse":" MBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649509048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649509048"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649531114","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649531114"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649532766","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649532766"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mboga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649554675","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649554674"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mboga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649556284","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649556283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mlima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIMA"," userResponse":" MLIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649568544","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649568543"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mlima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIMA"," userResponse":" MLIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649570168","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649570167"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mikono"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKONO"," userResponse":" MIKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649581295","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649581294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mikono"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MIKONO"," userResponse":" START_MIKONO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649583053","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649583053"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mikono"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKONO"," userResponse":" MIKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649584695","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649584694"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKULIMA"," userResponse":" MKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649595369","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649595369"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKULIMA"," userResponse":" MKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649596989","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649596989"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649605221","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649605221"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649606825","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649606824"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649629688","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649629688"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649631306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649631305"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649641448","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649641447"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649643064","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649643064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mende"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENDE"," userResponse":" MENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649647206","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649647205"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mende"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENDE"," userResponse":" MENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649648790","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649648790"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mahindi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHINDI"," userResponse":" MAHINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649662098","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649662098"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mahindi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHINDI"," userResponse":" MAHINDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649663712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649663711"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mdomo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649666412","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649666411"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mdomo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649668020","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649668019"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" meno"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649672965","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649672964"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" meno"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" MENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649674557","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649674556"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mjomba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBA"," userResponse":" MJOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649682152","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649682152"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mjomba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBA"," userResponse":" MJOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649684193","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649684191"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mjomba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649684283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649684283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mjomba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBA"," userResponse":" MJOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548649766249","data":{"timestamp":" 1548649766248"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_071951"," gameId":" b1de1e82-abfa-4b5e-b949-c5c627bd4974"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mjomba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}